http://www.somaluna.com/pages/no-parent-page/privacy-statement.html

Loading... Please wait...
Home
F.A.Q.
Incense Sticks & Smudge
Quality Sandalwood & Aloeswood (Agarwood)
Balsam
Champaca (Champa)
Popular Brands
The Mother's Fragrances Sun's Eye Satya Triloka Ophidian Farms Soma Luna Tara Aromatic Centre Flaires Nitiraj Baieido
See all brands
Our Newsletter
Want coupon codes monthly? Sign up today!
Your First Name:
Your Email Address:
Follow Us!
Want even more coupon codes? Follow us today!
HomePrivacy Statement
Privacy Statement
Soma Luna takes the protection of your online privacy very seriously. Please read the following to understand Soma Luna's privacy practices.What information does Soma Luna gather?Soma Luna may need to gather specific information from you at times such as your name and address, among other personal information. Information that is essential for Soma Luna to provide the services and/or products that are requested by you is generally designated as "Required". Additional information that would allow Soma Luna flexibility in providing its services or products, and may be used for internal statistical studies or market research, is generally indicated as "Optional". For example, a credit card number is required when ordering a product, whereas a phone number may not be essential, but would provide another means of communication between you and Soma Luna.How does Soma Luna use personal information?When you give Soma Luna information about yourself, you understand that you are agreeing to allow Soma Luna access to, storage of, and use of, the data that you give. Soma Luna may use the information you submit for any purposes related to Soma Luna's business, including, but not limited to, generating statistical studies, conducting market research, improving its products and services, sending you surveys, and notifying you of product upgrades and updates, new products, special offers and any other changes within Soma Luna that may affect you.How does Soma Luna handle credit card data?In order to protect our customers Soma Luna does not keep credit card numbers permanently in any of our computer systems. As soon as the order is successfully processed the credit card number is deleted from the system.Does Soma Luna share the information that it gathers with third parties?In a word, never. Soma Luna never sells or makes available any of your information to third parties. The only exception to this rule is in the case of requests for information by legal authorities.For further information, please Contact Us.
All prices are in USD
Copyright 2020 Soma Luna LLC.
Sitemap |
Copyright Notice |
Privacy Statement
